<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<wordList>
  <category id="0">
    <name>Biology</name>
    <words>
      <word>
        <name>Abdomen</name>
        <hint>The region between the pelvis and the thorax.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Cell Membrane</name>
        <hint>The double layer of lipids and proteins that surrounds a cell and separates the cytoplasm.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Photosynthesis</name>
        <hint>A process used by plants and other organisms to convert light energy into chemical energy</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Charles Darwin</name>
        <hint>The naturalist who created the theory of evolution.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Gregor Mendel</name>
        <hint>An Austrian monk who discovered the basic principles of genetic inheritance.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Binocular Vision</name>
        <hint>An animal who's eyes are projected forward, to which the field of view overlap, enabling the creature to judge depth.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Fungus</name>
        <hint>Eukaryotic heterotrophic organisms that live as saprophytes or parasites.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Host</name>
        <hint>An organism that can harbor or nourish another organism.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Lysis</name>
        <hint>The rupture and destruction of a cell, resulting in loss of cellular contents.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Pathogen</name>
        <hint>An organism that is capable of causing an infection, or harming a host cell.</hint>
      </word>
    </words>
  </category>
  <category id="1">
    <name>Chemistry</name>
    <words>
      <word>
        <name>Equilibrium</name>
        <hint>When a reaction reaches a position where it has no tendency to change.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Burette</name>
        <hint>A graduated glass tube with a tap at one end, for delivering known volumes of a liquid, especially in titrations.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Bulb-pipette</name>
        <hint>A volumetric piece of equipment which allows extremely accurate measurement of volume of a solution.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Marie Curie</name>
        <hint>The famous chemist who discovered Radium and Polonium.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Alfred Nobel</name>
        <hint>The famous chemist who invented the explosive Dynamite.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Bond Angle</name>
        <hint>The angle formed between two adjacent chemical bonds within the same atom.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Oxygen</name>
        <hint>A colourless, odourless reactive gas, which we breathe and is found in air.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Le Chatelier</name>
        <hint>A principle stating that if a constraint is applied to a system in equilibrium, equilibrium will shift to counteract the effect.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Mole Ratio</name>
        <hint>A ratio or fraction comparing the numbers of moles of any two components involved in a chemical reaction.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Reactant</name>
        <hint>The starting material for a chemical reaction.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Product</name>
        <hint>The substance formed as a result of a chemical reaction.</hint>
      </word>
    </words>
  </category>
  <category id="2">
    <name>Physics</name>
    <words>
      <word>
        <name>Acceleration</name>
        <hint>The rate of change of an object with respect to time.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Albert Einstein</name>
        <hint>German-born theoretical physicist.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Big Bang</name>
        <hint>The huge "explosion" 13.7 billion years ago.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Cosmic Rays</name>
        <hint>High speed, energetic particles in which are generated by our sun.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Black Hole</name>
        <hint>A region of empty space.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Dark Matter</name>
        <hint>Matter that gives out no light and does not interact with the electromagnetic force.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Stephen Hawking</name>
        <hint>A famous, well-known, theoretical physicist.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Gravity</name>
        <hint>The natural phenomenon by which all things with mass are brought toward one another.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Inertia</name>
        <hint>The resistance of any physical object to any change in its position and state of motion.</hint>
      </word>
      <word>
        <name>Universe</name>
        <hint>Everything that physically exists, including the entirety of space and time, all forms of matter, energy and momentum, and the physical laws and constants that govern them.</hint>
      </word>
    </words>
  </category>
 </wordList>